



About Me

Rooted and residing in Los Angeles, I am a designer that carries a passion for purposeful and engaging design. With a focus on the human aspect, I aim to go beyond mere usability and create experiences that resonate with users.

As a curious creative who is dedicated to growth and development, I actively pursue the exploration of new ideas and continuous learning.

Education

UX/UI Design UC Berkeley Ext.

Engineering Graphics and Design Technology Los Angeles Pierce College

Certifications

Automotive Service Technology

Fiat Chrysler Automobiles Performance Institute: Engine Diagnosis, Engine Management

Experience

Freelance

Graphic Designer, Production ArtistJul 2022 - Present

Fast Printing **Production Artist**Sep 2020 - Jun 2022

AKASHA

Creative Consultant

Jan 2020 - Present

Skills

Design:

Prototyping, Wireframing & page layout, Mockups, User research, Information architecture & site mapping, Interaction Design, Data synthesis & analysis

Tools:

Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe InDesign, Adobe Lightroom, Blender 3D

Code:

HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap, Github

Organizational:

Collaboration, Empathy, Adaptability, Mindfulness, Critical thinking